awear.com 2013-06-07

# A|wear - Privacy Policy Statement - A|wear

We at A|wear respect your right to privacy and comply with our obligations under the Data Protection Acts 1988 and 2003. The purpose of this Website Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) is to outline how we deal with any personal data you provide to us while visiting this website. Naturally, if you are not happy with this Policy you should not use this website.

By visiting this website, you are accepting the terms of this Policy. Any external links to other websites are clearly identifiable as such, and we are not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of these other websites.

Our Policy may change from time-to-time. Please check back periodically to see any updates to the Policy.

References in this Policy to "we", "us" and "A|wear" are to A|wear Ltd.

We at A|wear are committed to a progressive policy on privacy.

## What information do we collect and why?

As part of our newsletter sign-up process, we may ask for your email address, name, age, and preference of A|wear store. This is so that we may communicate to you personally, and so that we may tell you about changes to the website’s products and services, to tailor our communications to you so that we’re offering the most compelling information, and to inform you about promotions we may run from time-to-time.

When you go through the checkout process we ask for additional information, including billing address, delivery address, payment method details, and a password. We use this information to fulfill your order and to enable you to be able to login at a later time to track your order.

We may also gather information about how you use the website and aggregate this information with usage information from other customers to determine how to improve the website experience further. We use the non-personal data gathered from visitors to our website in an aggregate form to get a better understanding of where our visitors come from and to help us better design and organise our website.

Like most internet sites, we use Cookies to track your online experience on the website. Cookies are necessary to keep track of items in your basket, enable you to checkout, and to allow you to personalize your shopping experience. Cookies are required for the shopping experience. If you do not accept Cookies you will be unable to use this website. Refer to the FAQ content of your browser for more information on selecting or deselecting Cookies or for more details on the type of information that is stored by our cookies please [check our cookies information page >](http://www.awear.com/page/awear_cookie_policy)

## Third Parties

We share personal information with three separate parties in order to complete your transaction:

  * Our eCommerce Platform Provider. We pass along information so that they may process card transactions, screen for fraud, and conduct other activities integral to running a website. In addressing fraud prevention, we may disclose your address details to them to check against various Fraud Prevention Schemes
  * Our Carriers. We pass along your information to our carriers so that they may deliver your order to you.
  * Transaction Partners: We have a relationship with PayPal, and will send information to them for payment processing if you select that option during Checkout.

## What if you don't want to be contacted?

Not a problem. There are several ways to let us know about how you’d like to be communicated with:

  * If you have an account with us, log-on, select My Account, then Communicate with me, and change your preferences.
  * All emails contain information at the bottom of the email about how you can unsubscribe. Just follow these instructions.
  * Send an email to, writing “unsubscribe” in the subject heading.
  * Write to us at: eCommerce Customer Services, A|wear Ltd, A|wear Head Office, Creation House, Lemon Street, Dublin 2, Ireland.

As part of this agreement, we commit that we will not pass your information along to any third parties, except as outlined above, unless you have agreed for us to do so.

## Sale of Business

We reserve the right to transfer information (including your personal data) to a third party in the event of a sale, merger, liquidation, receivership or transfer of all or substantially all of the assets of our company provided that the third party agrees to adhere to the terms of the Policy and provided that the third party only uses your personal data for the purposes that you provided it to us. You will be notified in the event of any such transfer and you will be afforded an opportunity to opt-out.

## Security

Your personal data is held on secure servers hosted by  **Venda and Emarsys**. The nature of the Internet is such that we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us via the Internet. No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. However, we will take all reasonable steps (including appropriate technical and organisational measures) to protect your personal data.

## Updating, Verifying and Deleting Personal Data

You may inform us of any changes in your personal data, and in accordance with our obligations under the Data Protection Acts 1988 and 2003 we will update or delete your personal data accordingly. To find out what personal data we hold on you or to have your personal data updated, amended or removed from our database, please email us at  **[help@awear.com](mailto:help@awear.com?subject=Data%20Protection%20Query)**. Any such data subject requests may be subject to the prescribed fee.

## Transfers of Personal Data

It may be necessary, from time to time, for your personal data to be transferred to someone who provides a service to us in other countries, including countries outside of the European Economic Area (EEA). In addition your personal data may need to be stored in servers located outside the EEA. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing such personal data outside the EEA. If we do this, we will ensure that anyone to whom we pass your personal data agrees to treat your personal data with the same level of protection as if we were dealing with it.

## Changes to the Website Privacy Policy

Any changes to this Policy will be posted on this website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any time we decide to use personal data in a manner significantly different from that stated in this Policy, or otherwise disclosed to you at the time it was collected, we will notify you by email, and you will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in the new manner.

## Contact Us

If you would like to contact us, please email us at [feedback@awear.com](mailto:feedback@awear.com). If you send us an email, we will endeavour to respond to you within two business days.

This website is operated by:

Latzur Ltd t/a A|wear

A|wear Head Office

Creation House

Lemon Street

Dublin 2

Ireland

Company No: 509316 VAT REG: IE 9818896O  Copyright © Latzur Ltd t/a A|wear

* * *

1Specific rules apply to direct marketing, especially by electronic methods such as sms/email.
